mahindramarazzo.com 2018-11-05

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
We view protection of Your privacy as a very important principle. We understand clearly that You
and Your Personal Information is one of Our most important assets. We store and process Your
Information including any sensitive financial information collected (as defined under the
Information Technology Act, 2000), if any, on computers that may be protected by physical as well
as reasonable technological security measures and procedures in accordance with Information
Technology Act 2000 and Rules there under. If You object to Your Information being transferred or
used in this way please do not use Website.
Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination
practices.
Note:
Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of
any changes, please review this policy periodically.
By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If
you do not agree please do not use or access our Website.
By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal
information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and
subject to the Terms of Use.
1. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information
When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by
you from time to time. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and
customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your
needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly,
while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving
this purpose.
In general, You can browse the Website without telling us who You are or revealing any personal
information about yourself. Once you give us Your personal information, You are not anonymous to
us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always
have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on
the Website. We may automatically track certain information about You based upon your behaviour

on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics,
interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is
compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that You just
came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL
is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.
We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyse
our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies"
are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain
features that are only available through the use of a "cookie".
We also use cookies to allow You to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies
can also help us provide information that is targeted to Your interests. Most cookies are "session
cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from Your hard drive at the end of a session.
You are always free to decline our cookies if Your browser permits, although in that case You may
not be able to use certain features on the Website and You may be required to re-enter your
password more frequently during a session
Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website
that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.
If You choose to buy on the Website, we collect information about Your buying behaviour.
If You transact with us, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit /
debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument
details and tracking information from cheques or money orders.
If You choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave
feedback, we will collect that information You provide to us. We retain this information as necessary
to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.
If You send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties
send us correspondence about Your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such
information into a file specific to You.
We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, credit card /
debit card / other payment instrument details, etc.) from You when You set up a free account with
us. While You can browse some sections of our Website without being a registered member, certain

activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use Your contact information to
send You offers based on Your previous orders and Your interests.
2. Use of Demographic / Profile Data / Your Information
We use personal information to provide the services You request. To the extent we use Your
personal information to market to You, we will provide You the ability to opt-out of such uses. We
use Your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe
service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform You about
online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize Your experience; detect and
protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as
otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyse
demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Website.
We identify and use Your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer
our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify You and to gather broad demographic
information.
We will occasionally ask You to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for
contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or
income level). We use this data to tailor Your experience at our Website, providing You with content
that we think You might be interested in and to display content according to Your preferences.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later
read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information
specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in Your computer's hard
drive. The cookies do not contain any of Your personally identifiable information.
3. Sharing of personal information
We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect
and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple
accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that You

request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and
affiliates may not market to You as a result of such sharing unless You explicitly opt-in.
We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that
such      disclosure   is    reasonably      necessary      to    respond      to    summons,       court
orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices,
third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably
necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting
or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety
of our users or the general public.
We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of Your personal information with another business
entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-
organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur that other
business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with
respect to your personal information.
4. Links to Other Sites
Our Website (https://www.mahindramarazzo.com) links to other websites that may collect
personally identifiable information about You. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices
or the content of those linked websites.
5. Security Precautions
Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of
the information under our control. Whenever You change or access your account information, we
offer the use of a secure server. Once Your information is in our possession we adhere to strict
security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.
6. Choice/Opt-Out
We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional,
marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after
setting up an account.
If you want to remove your contact information from all www.mahindramarazzo.com lists and
newsletters, please visit www.mahindramarazzo.com/unsubscribe.

7. Advertisements on www.mahindramarazzo.com
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when You visit our Website. These
companies may use information (not including your name, address, email
address, or telephone number) about Your visits to this and other websites in order to provide
advertisements about goods and services of interest to You.
8. Your Consent
By using the Website and/ or by providing Your information, You consent to the collection and use
of the information You disclose on the Website in accordance with this privacy policy, including but
not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are
always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we
disclose it.
9. Grievance Officer
In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and
contact      details     of      the      Grievance      Officer      are      provided      below:
Mr. Abdul Syed
Head - Customer Experience
Email: SYED.ABDULHANIF@mahindra.com
A copy of this mail communication should also be marked to customercare@mahindra.com
